Email 

Password 

#### Why Have a CMN Hospitals Account?

* Create a fundraiser.
* Manage your recurring donations.
* Keep up to date with your local member hospital of CMN Hospitals.

Search our library  

Quick Links

Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals Privacy Policy
===================================================

Last Updated: October 20th, 2023

What this Privacy Policy Does and Does Not Cover
------------------------------------------------

This Privacy Policy covers how **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** (“Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals,” “we,” or “us”) treats personal information that we collect and receive through the **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** websites at [http://www.childrensmiraclenetworkhospitals.org/](https://www.childrensmiraclenetworkhospitals.org/) and [www.mymiracleband.org](https://mymiracleband.childrensmiraclenetworkhospitals.org/) and our “Give Miracles” mobile application (the “Services”). In this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of local children’s hospitals, companies that **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** does not own or control, or to people that **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** does not employ or manage.

Information Collection and Use
------------------------------

**Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** collects personal information when you donate directly to **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals**. If you donate directly to a hospital, then we may receive your personal information to the extent that the hospital shares it with us in accordance with its own privacy policy. When you donate, we ask for information such as your name, email address, and zip code. Once you donate to **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals**, you are not anonymous to us. When you use the Services, we may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address and the page you request, through automated means such as cookies. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the features of the Services. To the extent the information we automatically collect through the Services consists of, or is paired with, your personal information, we will treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may also use third-party analytics tools such as Google Analytics that collect information about use of the Services and user traffic). **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** uses information for the following general purposes: to improve our services, collect donations, contact you, conduct research, enforce our agreements, comply with applicable legal requirements and industry standards, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

Information Sharing and Disclosure
----------------------------------

We may disclose aggregated information about our donors, and information that does not identify any individual donor, without restriction. **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** will share your donor contact information with the **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** participating hospital selected during the donor’s gift designation. The donor is advised to review the receiving institution’s privacy policy to see how they will use their donor information. **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

* We disclose information to contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our services and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them;
* We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
* If we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Children’s Miracle Network Hospital’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law; and
* We will transfer information about you to a buyer or other transferee in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, sale, or other transfer of some or all of our assets. In this event, **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Correction/Updating Personal Information
----------------------------------------

You can change your donor information (name, address, etc.) in our database by contacting our customer support team at [801-214-7400](tel:801-214-7400), or by clicking [here](https://childrensmiraclenetworkhospitals.org/contact-us/). You may also reach out to our customer support team to request the deletion of your personal information, although we may not accommodate a request to change or delete information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. If you have received a promotional email from us, you can also opt out of receiving future promotional emails from us by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in such email. Donors who have previously opted-in to external communication lists and services can also use the above contacts to inform **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** that you no longer wish to have your personal information shared in this manner.

Confidentiality, Security, and Retention
----------------------------------------

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. In certain areas **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** uses industry-standard TLS-encryption to protect data transmissions

Do Not Track
------------

Your web browser may let you choose your preference as to whether you want to allow the collection of information about your online activities over time and across different websites or online services. At this time, the Services do not respond to the preferences you may have set in your web browser regarding such collection of your information, and the we may continue to collect information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

Children’s Personal Information
-------------------------------

The Services are not directed to, and **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from, children under the age of 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us as set forth below.

Data Transfers
--------------

**Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** is based in the State of Utah in the United States. When we obtain information about you, we may transfer, process, and store such information outside of the country in which you reside, including in the United States. By using the Services or by donating to us, you consent to the transfer to and processing and storage of your information in countries outside of your country of residence, which may have different data protection laws than those in the country where you reside.

CMN Hospitals SMS Terms and Conditions
--------------------------------------

By supplying Your mobile device number to the Website or any of our Microsites, you agree to receive text messages about the event for which You are registering, as well as information and promotion of other CMN Hospital activities. Agreement to receive this information is not required to participate in fundraising programs of CMN Hospitals. CMN Hospitals does not charge for any content, however, downloadable content may incur additional charges from your wireless carrier. You are solely responsible for any fees, including web access and/or data or text message charges that may be billed by your wireless carrier based on your individual plan.

#### Text Message Information

* CMN Hospitals does not charge for receiving or sending text messages to 34984.
* CMN Hospitals is not responsible for delays upon receiving text messages.
* You may sign up online or text **CMNHOSPITALS** to **34984** to receive our promotional and event text messages.
* By enrolling in the program, you certify that A) you are the account holder or B) have the account holder’s permission to do so.
* You must be 13 years of age or to participate in CMN Hospitals’ SMS campaign.
* Message frequency is 6 msgs per month. Message and Data Rates may apply.
* For additional information, text **HELP** to **34984**. You may opt-out at anytime by sending **STOP** to **34984**. Contact Us at **+1-888-209-7905** or [support@cmnhospitals.org](mailto:support@cmnhospitals.org) with any concerns.
* Carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.

Changes to This Privacy Policy
------------------------------

**Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** may update this Privacy Policy in its sole discretion. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your **Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. The date this Privacy policy was last updated is at the top of this page. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to check for any updates.

Contact Us
----------

If you have questions or suggestions, please send them to us by clicking [here](https://childrensmiraclenetworkhospitals.org/contact-us/).

**Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals** Customer Care – Privacy Policy Issues 205 West 700 South Salt Lake City, UT 84101 [801-214-7400](tel:801-214-7400)

USA - ENG

© 2024 Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals, a not-for-profit, section 501(c)(3)
